{
    "id": "7d6232f5429641659b46b161b2a372f6",
    "title": "Edit the passage",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b3790ef7ca0140e9b5d3c79e6a19d3ac",
            "title": "Gap Fills",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The auditorium was ............................ with buntings.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "decorating",
                        "decorated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Chairs ............................. neatly arranged in rows for the invitees.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dais ........................ a beautiful backdrop.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "has",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The principal .......................... the chief guest to the stage.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "escorted",
                        "was escorted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When they .............................. their seats, two girls sang the prayer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all occupied",
                        "were all occupied"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "After that the principal ............................ the annual report.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was reading",
                        "read"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Then the chief guest ........................... a brief speech.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "was made",
                        "has made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .............................. the students to work hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was advising",
                        "has advised",
                        "advised"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He said that they should aim at success and ............................ credit to the school.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bring",
                        "bringing",
                        "brought"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This ........................... by the prize distribution ceremony.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "followed",
                        "was followed",
                        "has followed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}